-室友早  -早
- Morning, roomie.  - Hey!
你今天早上终于记得穿衣服了
You remembered to put clothes on this morning.
事不过五嘛
Fifth day's a charm.
乔伊  能搬回来真好
Oh Joey, it's so great to be back here.
你真帮了我跟艾玛一个大忙
You're making it so easy on me and Emma.
你能回来也很好
It's great having you back.
要待多久就待多久
Stay as long as you want.
就是她什么时候才不会
And when does she stop
整宿的哭呢
crying all night?
你居然没有光着屁股
Hey! You're not naked.
瑞秋  你今晚什么时候回来
Rach, when will we expect to see you tonight?
我大概六点回来吧
I probably be back around 6.
她在房间里呢  已经收拾好了
But she's in the bedroom, all ready to go.
可她又睡着了  所以
But she did fell back to sleep, so
她可能因为昨晚忙着
She's probably exhausted from
制造美妙的哭声累坏了
all that adorable screaming she did last night.
-再见  -再见
- Bye.  - Bye.
希望艾玛没有给你带来太多麻烦
Hey, I hope Emma isn't making it too hard on you.
没  一切都很好
No, hey, it's been great.
我得跟你说  虽然瑞秋住在这
I just want you to know that with Rachel staying here...
但是我之前对她的感觉  已经没了
all my feelings from before are totally over.
即使本来还有
And even if they weren't
当你看到一个女人用吸奶器
when you walk in on a woman using a breast pump
-是啊  效果显著  -哇
- Yeah, that'll do it.  - Wow!
那你怎样呢
So how are you?
-不错啊  -真的吗
- I'm okay.  - Really?
当然  要是问我  有没有希望过
Sure. I mean, do I wish
可以和瑞秋幸福地生活在一起
me and Rachel living together would have worked out?
当然有
Of course. You know, I'm disappointed,
我只是有点失望  可毕竟这又不是离婚
but it's not like it's a divorce.
事实上这…
Well, actually it
这不是离婚  这不是离婚
It's not a divorce. It is not a divorce!
反正我跟瑞秋  都应该过自己的新生活了
Anyway, I think Rachel and I need to get on with our lives.
或许应该开始跟其他人交往
Maybe start seeing other people.
哇  真的吗
Wow. Really?
当然  为何不呢
Sure, why not?
其实  你认不认识适合我的人
In fact, if you know anyone that'd be good for me...?
当然  我认识很多女生
Sure. I know lots of girls.
想到谁了  说个名字
Any names come to mind?
还要名字
Names?
我正要吃东西  你要吗
I was about to eat. Want something?
有什么
What you got?
我看看  有豆泥 胡萝卜泥…
Okay, let's see, we got strained peas, strained carrots...
梅子泥  还没有试过这个
strained plums. We haven't tried that yet!
好棒
Goody!
谢谢
Thanks.
跟瑞秋重新住一起感觉如何
So how is it living with Rachel again?
当然  除了有很多好吃的之外
I mean, apart from the great food?
很好  很好  只是...
I'm fine, I'm fine. It's just....
她跟罗斯之间真的是很诡异
It's just weird what's happening with her and Ross.
昨天他居然要我介绍女生给他
Yesterday he asked me to fix him up with somebody.
瑞秋也问我有没有男生可以介绍给她
Rachel asked me if I knew anyone for her too.
-他们为什么要这样呢  -不知道
- Why are they doing this?  - I don't know.
他们彼此再适合不过了  真是神经
They're so perfect for each other. It's crazy.
你知道什么才神经  这些罐子是怎样
You know what's crazy?
才两口就没了
These jars. It's like two bits in here?
真希望他们可以发现  他俩是天生一对
I just wish they'd realize they should be together.
他们又住在一起的时候
I know, I know. When they moved in together,
我以为事情就解决了
I figured that's where things were headed.
我知道  他们应该是一家人
I know. They should be a family.
结婚生更多的小孩
They should marry and have more children.
是啊  还该把其中一个取名叫乔伊
Yes. And they should name one of their kids Joey.
我或许不会有小孩
I may not have kids.
总是要有人帮我把我的姓传下去
Someone's gotta carry on the family name.
或许他们一旦开始跟别人约会
You know what? Maybe once they start dating
知道别人是怎样的
and see what's out there
他们就会发现彼此是多么适合
they'll realize how good they are for each other.
因为他俩真是绝配啊
Yeah, because it is slim pickings.
我昨晚约会的女生遭透了  讨厌
I had this date last night. Yuck!
但我们说话小声点  她还在房间里
But we should probably keep it down, she's still in the bedroom.
那我们该怎么办
So, what are we gonna do?
难道真要帮他们介绍别人吗
Are we just gonna set them up with people?
那只会使他们渐行渐远
I know, that just pushes them further and further apart.
我知道要怎么做了
I know what we can do.
我们帮罗斯跟瑞秋介绍糟糕的约会对象
We could set Ross and Rachel up on horrible dates...
可以使他们意识到彼此才是归宿
so they'll realize how good they are together.
-真是好计划  -没错
- That's a great plan.  - Yeah.
你知道最棒的是什么吗
You know what the best part of it is?
我终于可以用到计划笑声了
I get to do my plan laugh.
停  不要那么大声  不要吵醒那个谁
Okay, shh! Not so loud. We don't want to wake up
你们今晚没事  对吗
Hi. You guys aren't doing anything tonight, are you?
你凭什么这么以为呢
See, now, why would you assume that?
就因为我们是已婚吗
Just because we're married?
我要让你知道 我们可是非常时髦又充实的
I mean, I will have you know that we are very hip, happening people.
现在  不好意思
Now if you'll excuse me,
我要继续读报上的讣告了
I have to get back to reading the obituaries.
我就是问问  因为今晚我需要人帮我带艾玛
I was just asking because I need someone to watch Emma tonight.
我们当然帮你带  你要干什么去
Sure we'll do it. What are you up to?
菲比帮我安排一个约会
Well, Phoebe set me up on a date.
我的天
Oh, my God.
怎么了  有什么不对吗
Why? What's the big deal?
我以为你跟罗斯是...
I figured because you and Ross are--
是怎样  一年半前上过床吗
What? Slept together a year and a half ago?
是啊  我已经好了
Yeah, I'm all set.
我觉得你去约会是件好事
I think it's great you're going on a date.
听起来很健康
It sounds healthy.
你也有你的需要
I mean, you have needs.
放手拥抱你的女性特质吧
Embrace your womanhood.
你要找工作吗
You want a job?
少看欧普拉  多投简历去
Turn off Oprah and send out  resume.
我大概七点带她过来好吗
I'll bring her by around 7, okay?
没问题
That's perfect.
你们会过很开心的
You guys are gonna have so much fun.
她现在正是可爱的时候
She's at such a cute age.
几件事注意一下  现在她会吃固体食物了
A couple things. Now that she eats solid food,
所以会按时排便
she poops around the clock.
还有小心你的头发  她喜欢抓着不放
And watch out for your hair because she likes to grab it.
她这个年龄阶段
She's also in this phase
还会在你离开房间的时候拼命尖叫  但是...
where if you leave the room, she screams, but....
谢啦  祝你们玩得开心
Thanks, you guys. Have fun.
突然间  我希望读到讣告里有自己的名字
Suddenly I wish I was reading my own name.
乔伊  我好兴奋
Joey, hey. I'm so excited.
我给瑞秋找了一个最糟糕的男人
I set Rachel up with the worst guy.
好的  他怎么样
All right. Who is he?
是我按摩过的一个男客户  按摩时
It's a guy I used to massage. By ''massage'' ...
我得按住他  让他不能转身露鸟
I mean hold down so he wouldn't turn over and flash me.
等你听听我给罗斯介绍的谁再说吧
Wait till you hear who I got for Ross.
喔  好啊
Oh, yeah.
这个女人特别无聊  是个老师
Okay. She's this really boring woman. She's a teacher.
老师
A teacher?
她喜欢历史跟外国影片
She's into history and foreign movies.
而且她还喜欢益智游戏
And she loves puzzles.
拜托  谁会喜欢益智游戏呢
Come on, who loves puzzles?
嗯  罗斯喜欢啊
Well, Ross does.
你把计划给毁了
You're ruining the plan!
乔伊  你这是要给他介绍完美伴侣呢
Joey, you fixed him up with his perfect woman.
-我的天  你说的没错  -是啊
- Oh, my God, you're right!  - Yeah.
她甚至还喜欢读书
She even reads for pleasure!
你怎么会认识那种女人的
How do you know a woman like that?
我就不能认识聪明的女人吗
I'm not allowed to know smart women?
乔伊
Joey?
我到图书馆里去上厕所认识的
We met at the library. I went in to pee.
-那我们现在该怎么办呢  -嗯  好吧
- So now what do we do?  - Well, okay.
我打电话跟她取消
I'll call her and tell her the date's canceled
然后再找别人吧
and find him somebody else.
要是我们不找别人呢
What if we don't find him somebody else?
我们只跟女的说约会取消了
We'll just tell her the date's off...
但是不告诉罗斯
...but we don't tell Ross.
他就会在餐厅等着被放鸽子了
He'll go to the restaurant and get stood up.
你好坏哦
I hear that's bad.
太棒了  瑞秋会有个糟糕的约会
So this is great. Rachel's gonna have a terrible date
罗斯被放鸽子
Ross gets stood up,
之后  他们会意识到对方有多么好
and then they'll realize how good they have it together.
是的  好计划
Yes, the plan.
这不是圣诞老公公的计划
It's not Santa's plan.
不  是这样…
No, it's....
有点不太好玩了
Yeah, you know, it's not that fun.
是不好玩  被我们弄僵了
No, I think we killed it.
艾玛  看着我
Emma? Emma, look at me!
那么  我要下楼待一会
Well, I think I'll go downstairs for a while.
不要  没事的  我没有去
No, no, no! It's okay! It's okay! I didn't go!
别哭  我是开玩笑的
Don't cry, it's just a bit!
我是你的钱德勒姑父
I'm your Uncle Chandler.
我只会搞笑啊
Funny is all I have!
告诉你  我从明天开始到六号都在排卵
Okay, just so you know, I'm gonna be ovulating from tomorrow until the 6th.
所以接下来的四十八小时
So don't touch yourself
你不要自慰
for the next 48 hours.
我不自慰的
I don't do that.
我会试着克制自己
I'll try to stop.
-你是说到六号吗  -是啊
- Did you say until the 6th?  - Yeah.
今天就是六号
Today is the 6th.
不  不是
No, it's not.
是的  而且是2003年
Yes, it's also 2003.
我的天  今天是六号了
Oh, my God. Today's the 6th?
我可能已经停止排卵了
I may be done ovulating!
我也可能在餐厅卖了有问题的肉
I may have also served some very questionable meat at the restaurant.
-去做测试  看是不是还排  -好的
- Go take the test, see if we're okay.  - Okay.
定力不错啊
Tough crib.
其他的排卵测试棒呢
Hey, where are all my ovulation sticks?
这只剩下一个了
There's only one here.
我可能拿了几个
I might have checked to see
测我是不是在排卵
if I was ovulating a couple times.
钱德勒
Chandler!
我没有工作  没事做很痛苦的
I'm not working! There's not much to do around here!
不好意思
Excuse me.
有没有女人在吧台那等人呢
Is there a woman waiting at the bar?
中等身高  黑发
Someone average height, dark hair?
可能在玩猜谜游戏
Or perhaps doing a puzzle?
只有一个中国醉汉
There's a drunk Chinese guy.
如果我一小时之后还在这里
Well, if I'm still here in an hour,
给他上杯酒  算我账上
buy him a drink on me.
您要不要再点一杯红酒
Can I get you another glass of wine?
不知道  我不想喝到醉醺醺的  然后...
I don't know if I should. I don't want to be drunk when I...
独自回家
...go home alone tonight.
被放鸽子了  是吗
Got stood up, huh?
没有什么  只不过是跟陌生人约会
It's no big deal. It's just a blind date.
你是担心那个女的
Are you worried your date came,
进来看你一眼就走了吗
saw you and left?
没有
No!
还好  我还在排卵
We're okay. I'm still ovulating.
很好  因为今天下午四点的时候
Oh, good, because as of 4:00 this afternoon,
我没有在排卵
I am not.
那我们搞起来吧
So let's do this.
-我想我没办法  -不是吧
- I don't think I can.  - Oh, come on.
我知道你不再是十八岁了
I know you're not 18 anymore,
给它一点时间嘛
but give it a minute.
-因为艾玛在  -天啊  艾玛
- Because of Emma.  - Oh, my God, Emma.
亲爱的  我忘记你在这里了
Oh, sweetie, I forgot you were here.
说的对  我们不能这么做
You're right, we can't do this.
也不能把她单独留在这里
We can't leave her alone.
对不起
Sorry.
除非…
Unless...
或许我们可以在这里做
maybe we do it here.
她这个年纪懂什么
I mean, how much can she even be aware of at this age?
她已经能意识到  我们有没有离开房间
She's aware when we leave a room.
或许她也会注意到我们…
She may notice if we start...
在滚床单
...canoodling in it.
滚床单
Canoodling?
嗯  我总不能在一个娃娃面前说…
Well, I can't say hump or screw...
做爱或是上床吧
in front of the B-A-B-Y.
我想  在婴儿面前做爱…
I don't know, I guess having sex in front of a baby...
-并没有那么...  -可怕  吓人
- isn't so....  - Horrifying? Scarring?
让人蹲监狱的错
Something people go to jail for?
-大概你说得对  -大概我说得对
- I guess you're right.  - You guess I'm right?
那次住在宾馆的时候
When we at that bed-and-breakfast,
你不肯和我做爱
you wouldn't have sex with me
是因为你觉得
because you thought
有只鹿站在窗外盯着看
a deer was staring through the window.
什么变态混蛋
Well, what kind of a sick bastard
会想在一只鹿面前做爱啊
wants to do it in front of a deer?
哇  看上去都挺好吃
Wow, everything looks so good.
我要点个鸡肉
I think I'm gonna have the chicken.
我必须要说
I just have to say this.
你可真美
You're really beautiful.
嘴真甜  谢谢你
Wow, that's very sweet. Thank you.
我长得有点可笑
I'm kind of funny-looking.
-什么  -我是说  拜托
- What?  - Look, I mean, come on...
你可不是我可以高攀的起的
...you're way out of my league.
这里人人都看得出来
Everybody in here knows it.
我敢说那边那个人  正在这么说
I bet that guy over there is probably saying:
"她怎么会跟他约会呢"
''Why's she out with him?"
"一定是他很有钱"
"He must be rich.''
可是  我没钱
Well, I'm not.
你想吃点什么
What do you think you want to order?
我好想吃这家的鸡肉
I'm real excited about that chicken.
我也不风趣
I'm not funny, either.
所以如果你是在想
So if you were thinking,
"他长得不怎么样"
"Well, he's not that good-looking..."
"但也许他是个幽默的人"
"but maybe we'll have some laughs,''
那你就错了
that ain't gonna happen.
别这样  史提夫
Well, come on, Steve,
别打断我紧张的苦笑
let's not rule out nervous laughter.
等等  菲比告诉我
Hey, now, wait a minute, Phoebe told me
你自己有家餐厅  很了不起啊
that you owned your own restaurant. That's impressive.
已经没了  因为吸毒
I lost it to drugs.
我现在卖印的T恤
I silk-screen T-shirts now.
真的啊  工作怎么样
Really? What's that like?
做一个你痛恨  又赚不到钱的工作
It's really fulfilling doing something
真是非常充实啊
you hate for no money.
没错  我没有钱  我不风趣
That's right. I have no money, I'm not funny...
我还住在一个  只有一室的房子里
I live in a studio apartment
还是跟两个男人合租的
with two other guys.
我还很确定  我有不育症
And I'm pretty sure l'm infertile.
别这样  别这样  史提夫
Now, come on. Come on, Steve.
你肯定有对自己满意的地方
There must be something that you like about yourself.
我倒是挺满意我的头发
I do like my hair.
真的吗
Really?
-哈啰  -菲比  是我
- Hello?  - Phoebe, it's me!
我一定要追杀到你  然后把你给剁了
I'm going to hunt you down and kill you.
嘿  瑞秋
Hey, Rach!
这真是史上最烂的约会
This is the worst date ever!
你怎么给我介绍这么个怪胎
How could you set me up with this creep?
听着  你说的可是
You know, you are talking about
我最要好  最要好的朋友
one of my dear, dear friends.
我才不管  这人简直就是个恶梦
I don't care. This guy is a nightmare.
好了  他只在嗑完药的时候
All right, so he gets a little crazy
才有点失常
when he's stoned.
他没嗑药
He's not stoned.
他有出去抽烟吗
Did he go out for a cigarette?
-有啊  四次  -我亲爱的甜姐儿瑞秋
- Yeah. Four times.  - My dear, sweet Rach.
我们的计划奏效了
Well, our plan is working.
瑞秋现在如坐针毡
Rachel's having a miserable time...
而罗斯被人放了鸽子
and Ross is stood up somewhere at a restaurant
正在某家餐厅里呆坐
all alone.
他们很快就会重归于好
Pretty soon they'll be back together.
等到大家发现我们做的好事时
By the time anyone's figured out what we've done,
我们早就在阳光普照的墨西哥了
we'll be in sunny Mexico.
等等  这是另一个计划的结局
Oh, wait, that's the end of a different plan.
她睡着了  钱德勒
She's asleep. Chandler?
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
艾玛也这样做啊
Emma was doing it.
她睡着了
She's asleep.
她睡了  那就表示我们可以…
She's asleep. That means we can....
是的  但是我们动作必须要快
Yes. But we have to be fast.
好的  我尽量
Oh, okay, I'll try.
那你不能发出任何声音
And you can't make any noise.
好啦  我尽量
Okay, I'll try.
有人吗
Hello?
艾玛
Emma?
嘿  嗨
Hey! Hi!
你好吗  你好吗
How are you? How are you?
你的保姆们呢  嗯
Where are your babysitters, huh?
卧房的门怎么关了
Why is the bedroom door closed?
在照顾哇哇的时候
You can't have S-E-X
怎么能上床啊
when you're taking care of a B-A-B-I-E.
有个坏消息  那个中国人走了
I've got bad news. The Chinese guy left.
命里有时终须有
If it was meant to be,
命里无时莫强求
it's meant to be.
被放鸽子又能怎么样
Look, you got stood up. Who cares?
让我们来好好招待你
We're gonna show you a good time.
你就坐着享受吧
Sit and relax.
事实上  我要免费招待您一个
In fact, let me bring you
蟹肉饼开胃菜吧
a crab-cake appetizer on the house.
哇  免费的蟹肉饼吗  真是周到
Wow, free crab cakes? Well, that's nice.
虽然我本来希望今晚可以嘿咻一下的
Although I was hoping to have sex tonight.
只要蟹肉饼就行了
Just the crab cakes.
你在干嘛  是要让他留下来吗
What are you doing? Are you trying to get him to stay?
你不能这样做
You can't do that.
不要多管闲事好吗
Just get out of here, okay?
很抱歉  这是怎么回事
I'm sorry, what's going on?
服务生们都在打赌
Okay, the waiters have a little pool going.
赌你会等多久
We have a bet on how long it'll take
才会放弃回家去
before you give up and go home.
什么
What?!
你竟然拿我的痛苦来赢钱
You're making money off my misery?
只要你待到九点二十的话  我就赢了
Well, if you stay till 9:20, I am.
太离谱了
This is unbelievable.
我一生从未被如此羞辱过
I have never been so insulted in my life.
现在  如果你帮我把蟹肉饼打包
Now, if you'll wrap up my free crab cakes,
我就马上离开
I'll be on my way.
真是奇怪
Well, that was weird.
你倒是很大声  反而我倒是挺快的
You were loud and I was fast.
我觉得我们这一次会成功
I think we may have really done it this time.
都等不及去作验孕测试
I wish l didn't have to wait to take a pregnancy test.
你可能需要再多买一些
You may want to get some more of those too.
艾玛呢
Where's Emma?
我的天  艾玛呢  艾玛呢
Oh, my God, where's Emma? Where's Emma?
别问我
Don't ask me.
我跟你一起在里面滚床单呢
I was in there canoodling you.
一定是瑞秋提早回来
Okay. Okay. I'm sure that Rachel came home early
把艾玛带回去了
and picked up Emma.
你去对面看看  我来打电话给她
You go look across the hall, and I'll call her cell.
你最好祈祷我有怀孕
You better hope we're pregnant...
因为无论如何
because one way or another,
我们都得有个孩子还给瑞秋
we're giving a baby back to Rachel!
不敢相信我在你面前哭了
I can't believe I'm crying in front of you.
你一定觉得我很可悲
You must think I'm so pathetic.
不  不  不  我欣赏会哭的男人
No, no, no, I admire a man who can cry.
-真的  -别碰我的外套
- Really?  - Don't touch my coat.
对不起  我有电话
Sorry, that's my phone.
-哈啰  -嘿  瑞秋  约会如何
- Hello?  - Hey, Rach, how's it going?
我的天  这是我有过最烂的约会了
Oh, my God, this is the worst date ever.
喔  少来了
Oh, come on.
听着  我很抱歉
Look, you know what, I'm sorry,
但你觉得一切进行的很顺利吗
but did you really think that this was going well?
-怎么了  -你有来过吗
- What's up?  - Hey, did you stop by here?
-没有  -我的天  那…
- No.  - Oh, my God! Then....
感谢上帝  艾玛  原来你在这里
Thank God! Emma, there you are!
"原来你在这里"是什么意思
What? What do you mean, ''there you are''?
她刚才在哪里
Where was she?
我们在玩躲猫猫
We were playing peekaboo.
她爱死我的激情演出了
She loves it when I'm dramatic.
你为什么要带走她
Why the hell did you take her?
因为你们两个在做爱
Because you two were having sex!
-不  我们没有  -别对我说谎
- No, we weren't.  - Don't you lie to me.
我从钱德勒的头发就可以看出来
I can tell by Chandler's hair.
你也太懒了  就不能有一次在上面吗
You are so lazy. Can't you get on top for once?
好啦  好啦  我们是在做爱
All right. All right, we were.
我们是要努力怀孕
We're trying to make a baby.
莫妮卡正在排卵
Monica's ovulating.
艾玛就在隔壁
It's unacceptable that you'd have sex
你们居然在里面做爱  不能接受
with Emma in the next room.
我必须要告诉瑞秋这件事
I'll have to tell Rachel about this.
拜托不要  她会杀了我们的
Please don't. She will kill us.
我一定要  除非…
Hey, I gotta. Unless....
除非怎样
Unless what?
除非你们把第一个小孩
Unless you name
取名叫乔伊
your first-born child Joey.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
我可能永远都不会有小孩
Hey, I may never have kids...
总是要有人帮我延续香火
and somebody's gotta carry on
用我家的姓吧
my family name.
你姓崔比安尼
Your family name is Tribbiani.
我差点就被你骗到了
You almost had me.
听着...
Look...
虽然我知道问也是白问
I think I know the answer to this question,
但是…
but...
你想要跟我做爱吗
would you like to make love to me?
真的  真的不想
Really, really not.
只不过是问问
It's just as well.
反正也起不来
It doesn't work anyway.
好吧  那就这样  晚安  史提夫
All right, well, that's good to know. Good night, Steve.
怎么了
Hey, what's wrong?
我刚度过糟糕的一晚
I just had a rough night.
要蟹肉饼吗
Crab cake?
发生什么事了
Well, what happened?
跟你聊这件事真的是有点奇怪 但是…
This is kind of weird to talk to you about this, but--
莫妮卡跟我说你去约会了
Monica told me you had a blind date.
-是啊 -我也是
- Yeah.  - I did too.
但是如果对方没有出现
But is it technically a date
那到底算不算是约会呢
if the other person doesn't show up?
你是不是觉得  她看到你就走了
Oh, no. Do you think she walked in, saw you and left?
大家为什么一直这样说
Why does everyone keep saying that?
我可以让你好过点
If it makes you feel any better,
我真希望我的对象没有出现
I wish my date hadn't shown up.
那么糟吗
That bad?
他是做T恤的
Well, he makes T-shirts for a living...
而且他认为送这样的礼物给我是…
...and he thought it would be appropriate to give me...
很适当的
this.
"女性身体检查官"
''Female Body Inspector''?
这是什么尺寸的
What size is that?
等等  所以他们要
Now wait a minute. So they're gonna
把第一个孩子取名叫乔伊
name their first child Joey?
那我要怎样才能
How do I get them
让他们把第二个孩子
to name the next one
以我的名字取名呢
after me?
很简单  你只要
It's easy. You just walk in
在他们做爱时走进去就行了
on them having sex.
那他们已经欠我三个菲比了
Oh, so they owe me, like, three Phoebes.
我的天  瞧  那是罗斯跟瑞秋
Oh, my God! Look, it's Ross and Rachel!
计划奏效了
The plan is working!
别再做那个计划笑声了
Don't do the plan laugh.
我们几个月以来的第一次约会
The first dates we've had in months,
结果却都这么惨
and they were both such disasters.
你想啊  有点奇怪...
You know, it is weird...
菲比帮我安排一个很烂的约会
...that Phoebe would set me up on a date that was awful...
而在同一晚
...on the same night
乔伊帮你安排了一个
Joey set you up on a date
根本没有人出现的约会
that didn't even show.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你不会认为这是故意的吧
You don't think it was intentional?
我是说  这实在太愚蠢了
I mean, that's just stupid.
我们真是天才
We're geniuses.
瞧瞧他们  合得不得了
Look at them! They're really bonding.
再度坠入爱河了
They're falling in love all over again.
他们看到我们了
Oh, they see us.
他们看起来很生气
Oh, they look mad.
他们知道了
They figured it out.
他们过来了  快跑
They're coming. Run!
-跑去哪  -墨西哥
- Where?  - Mexico!
谁敢相信她们居然还没有出现
Can you believe they're still not here?
是啊  四人约会
I know. A double blind date
我们竟然一起被放鸽子
and we both get stood up.
太倒霉了
What are the chances?
对啊  我好难过啊
I know, I'm so bummed.
现在可以上免费的蟹肉饼了吗
Could we have our free crab cakes now?
-什么  -我们被放鸽子了
- What?  - We've been stood up.
我们想要免费的蟹肉饼
And we want our free crab cakes.
你们俩  不用装了
Guys, give it a rest.
今晚没有人拿你们打赌
Nobody's betting on you tonight.
不过我们倒是在赌
Although we do have a pool going to see
看那个男的多久才会哭出来
how long it takes that guy to cry.
我的手好肥
I have such fat hands!